## BRYAN CLARK

Carlsbad, CA 92008

bryan.j.clark08@gmail.com

I love thinking about how to create value from data, particularly as it relates to building better experiences for customers. Ultimately, my ideal role blends product thinking with data expertise to identify, test (e.g. experiment), and operationalize new processes and experiences.

# **EDUCATION**

#### NEW YORK UNIVERSITY, STERN SCHOOL OF BUSINESS

New York, NY

Master of Business Administration; Specializations in Tech Product Management & Strategy

2020-2022

- Dean's List with Distinction (top 10% of graduating class)
- Teaching fellow (TF) for Tech Product Management 1 and 2

## BOSTON UNIVERSITY, METROPOLITAN COLLEGE

Master of Science, Applied Business Analytics

Boston, MA 2017-2018

• Teaching assistant (TA) for Data Mining for Business

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**NOOM** (Health & Wellness Behavioral Change Platform)

Product Manager, CRM Platform (Nov 2022 - Jan 2023)

New York, NY

2021-2023

- Conducted weekly user interviews to develop strategy and roadmap for scaling experimentation for email, push and SMS channels as a lever for delivering business value
- Partnered with data science to identify and prioritize opportunities for targeting improvements
- Led evaluation and implementation of a reverse ETL tool (Hightouch) to reduce engineering resources needed to update user profiles and serve machine learning model scores to messaging platform (Iterable)
- Improved email deliverability during peak season through database list hygiene and implementing monitoring / alerting for degradation (as measured by days >99% deliverability)

## Senior Data Scientist (Jan 2021 - Oct 2022)

- Developed and tested multi-arm bandit model to optimize emails offers that led to +4% yield in LTV (built model, email campaigns, and experiment without engineering resources)
- Deployed lead scoring ML model that improved incremental LTV yield of monthly email targeting by 3x
- Developed risk model to help product managers make experiment decisions based on downside risk
- Developed / launched experiments with Facebook Ads custom audiences to improve spend efficiency via uplift modeling
- Mentored summer data science intern to a full-time offer (prior to their senior year of college)
- Interviewed over 100 data scientist candidates (SQL and general skill assessment)

#### **DASHLANE** (Password Manager)

Data Scientist (Sept 2019 - Dec 2021)

New York, NY

2019-2020

- Designed and launched campaign experiment that improved free trial conversion by >200% (executed 1x a quarter)
- Created internal Python module that enabled faster analyzing of A/B testing for product analysts
- Partnered with the User Research team to lead internal focus groups to deliver a better experience for insights consumers
- Mentored junior members of the analytics team

# **H&M** (Clothing Retailer)

New York, NY

2018-2019

- Data Scientist, North America (Aug 2018 Aug 2019)
- Analyzed online customers to surface and evangelize the most profitable segment that was being underserved in CRM
- Taught merchants how to leverage the R programming language to speed up an excel workflow

**PETCO** (Pet Retailer)

San Diego, CA

2017-2018

Data Scientist (Jan 2018 - Sep 2018)

**Business Process Analyst, Repeat Delivery** (Jul 2017 - Jan 2018)

MBA Intern, Real Estate Data Science (Mar 2017 - Jul 2017)

• Won Petco Innovation Contest twice as part of a three-person team (2017, Next Gen Store; 2018, Culture)